<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>孙三狗的博客</title>
  
  <subtitle>天空才是上限，梦想总会实现</subtitle>
  <link href="https://jasper0629.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://jasper0629.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2022-04-18T07:45:24.403Z</updated>
  <id>https://jasper0629.github.io/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>孙三狗</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>自我介绍</title>
    <link href="https://jasper0629.github.io/2022/04/18/%E8%87%AA%E6%88%91%E4%BB%8B%E7%BB%8D-1/"/>
    <id>https://jasper0629.github.io/2022/04/18/%E8%87%AA%E6%88%91%E4%BB%8B%E7%BB%8D-1/</id>
    <published>2022-04-18T07:40:11.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-04-18T07:45:24.403Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>​Dear professors and teachers，good morning . Thank you for giving me the opportunity for this interview. My name is Sun Qianpu , 22 years old, and I come from Qiqihar. I’m a graduating college student from Tianjin University of Science and Technology, and majoring in Computer Science.</p><p>​During the four years in college, while successfully completing undergraduate studies I develop hobbies such as photography editing. In the second semester of my junior year, I learned about the field of Natural Language Processing and study independently the knowledge of artificial intelligence such as machine learning and fundamentals of NLP . I will try my best to do what I wanna do, no matter how difficult it is,  no matter what the result is  . If I have the opportunity, I hope I can study for a doctorate to further my study. I think I should spend my whole life studying and making my own contribution to the subject, even if only a little. Besides, I have excellent social skills. I have the confidence to handle the chores of life while maintaining high-quality postgraduate study</p><p>​Finally, I’d like to thank the teachers for giving me this precious opportunity. I hope I could have the opportunity to complete my postgraduate courses in Tsinghua University, which I have been longing for a long time</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;​	Dear professors and teachers，good morning . Thank you for giving me the opportunity for this interview. My name is Sun Qianpu , 22 year</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="复试" scheme="https://jasper0629.github.io/tags/%E5%A4%8D%E8%AF%95/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>pytorch</title>
    <link href="https://jasper0629.github.io/2022/04/18/pytorch/"/>
    <id>https://jasper0629.github.io/2022/04/18/pytorch/</id>
    <published>2022-04-18T06:08:07.000Z</published>
    <updated>2022-04-18T06:08:07.517Z</updated>
    
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
